{
    "subject": "resource/Yemen",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Abd_Rabbuh_Mansur_Hadi",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Yemen is Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8382853269577026,
            "question": "Who is Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7972381711006165,
            "question": "What is the capital of Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6654101014137268,
            "question": "What year did Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi become the president of Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6552201509475708,
            "question": "Who was the president of Yemen before Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5697742700576782,
            "question": "Name a prominent city in Yemen besides its capital."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.267546683549881,
            "question": "Is Sana'a a city in Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18210889399051666,
            "question": "Describe the geography of Yemen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1480645090341568,
            "question": "What is the official language of Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10737642645835876,
            "question": "What is the current political situation in Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10240686684846878,
            "question": "What are some major challenges facing Yemen today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Yemen is Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8955_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the current political situation in Yemen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8955_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the official language of Yemen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8955_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the geography of Yemen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8955_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8955_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The triple \"The capital of Yemen is Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi\" is incorrect according to the documents.\n\nHere is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information that supports the statement \"The capital of Yemen is Abd Rabbuh Mansur Hadi.\" The documents discuss President Abd Rabbuh Mansour Hadi and his role in relation to the capital city, but they do not state that he is the capital itself. According to the given context, Sanaa remains the constitutional capital of Yemen, with Aden being declared as a temporary capital by President Abdrabbuh Mansur Hadi due to security concerns."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}